Guide to the Charles E. Palm papers,1956-1986.
Palm, Charles E. papers,1956-1986.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Charles E. Palm papers, 1956-1986.
21-2-1478
Charles E. Palm
82 cubic ft.
Correspondence, typescripts, reports, drafts, handwritten notes, publications, and papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, typescripts, reports, drafts, handwritten notes of telephone conversations, and publications pertaining to his deanship of the New York State College of Agriculture from 1959 to 1972 and to his work as Liberty Hyde Bailey Professor of Agricultural Sciences beginning in 1972. The papers mainly document the administration and growth of the New York State College of Agriculture, its departments, committees, and related activities, including the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, the New York State Cooperative Extension Service, and the Water Resources Center; the relation of the New York State College of Agriculture with Cornell University, state and federal governments, and other organizations, including the New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, the United States Department of Agriculture, and the United States Agency for International Development, the Ford Foundation, the Rockefeller Foundation, the Foundation for American Agriculture, the National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council, the National Science Foundation, the National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, Agway, the New York State Horticultural Society, the New York State Grange, and the State University of New York. Subjects include the Office of International Agricultural Development's Chapingo and Los Baños Projects in Mexico and the Philippines, and the New York State Cooperative Extension Service (including 4-H).
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dean, New York State College of Agriculture, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, typescripts, reports, drafts, handwritten notes of telephone conversations, and publications pertaining to his deanship of the New York State College of Agriculture from 1959 to 1972 and to his work as Liberty Hyde Bailey Professor of Agricultural Sciences beginning in 1972. The papers mainly document the administration and growth of the New York State College of Agriculture, its departments, committees, and related activities, including the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, the New York State Cooperative Extension Service, and the Water Resources Center; the relation of the New York State College of Agriculture with Cornell University, state and federal governments, and other organizations, including the New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, the United States Department of Agriculture, and the United States Agency for International Development, the Ford Foundation, the Rockefeller Foundation, the Foundation for American Agriculture, the National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council, the National Science Foundation, the National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, Agway, the New York State Horticultural Society, the New York State Grange, and the State University of New York. Subjects include the Office of International Agricultural Development's Chapingo and Los Baños Projects in Mexico and the Philippines, and the New York State Cooperative Extension Service (including 4-H).
Also, the College of Agriculture Advisory Council, the Cornell University Division of Biological Sciences, the College of Agriculture Television Project, student dissent and protest, McDonald Farms, Uihlein Farms, and the Miner Institute, agricultural research and economics, international agriculture and the world food supply, the expanded use of pesticides and the sociological implications of their application, environmentalism, the Adirondack Study Commission, Alpha Zeta, agricultural labor, migrant labor, and the Cohn Farm controversy, the Agricultural Policy Accountability Project, the vegetable, fruit and wine industries, the food processing and marketing industries, and the New York State sugar beet industry. Major correspondents include Morton Adams, Donald W. Barton, Charles Dana Bennett, Maurice C. Bond, Damon Boynton, Earl L. Butz, Orville L. Freeman, Deane W. Malott, Leland Spencer, Nyle C. Brady, Dale R. Corson, Edmund H. Fallon, W. Keith Kennedy, Joseph P. King, Thomas E. LaMont, Deane W. Malott, T. Norman Hurd, William I. Myers, James A. Perkins, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Edward H. Smith, Kenneth L. Turk, and D.L. Umali.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Palm, Charles E.; Adams, Morton.; Boynton, Damon.; Brady, Nyle C.; Butz, Earl L.; Corson, Dale R.; Fallon, Edmund H.; Freeman, Orville L.; Hurd, T. Norman.; Kennedy, W. Keith.; King, Joseph P.; LaMont, Thomas.; Malott, Deane W.(Deane Waldo), 1898-; Myers, William I.(William Irving), 1891-1976.; Perkins, James Alfred, 1911-; Rockefeller, Nelson A.(Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979.; Smith, Edward H.; Spencer, Leland.; Turk, Kenneth L.; Umali, D.L.; Adirondack Study Commission.; Agway Inc.; Alpha Zeta.; Association of Land-Grant Colleges.; Cohn Farm.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University.; Cornell University.Division of Biological Sciences.; Ford Foundation.; Foundation for American Agriculture.; McDonald Farms.; National Research Council (U.S.); National Science Foundation.; New York (State).Dept. of Agriculture and Markets.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.; New York State Agricultural Extension Service.; New York State College of Agriculture--Administration.; New York State College of Agriculture--Faculty.; New York State College of Agriculture--Funds and scholarships.; New York State College of Agriculture.Extension Service.; New York State Grange.; New York State Horticultural Society.; Rockefeller Foundation.; State University of New York.; Uihlein Farms.; United States Agency for International Development.; United States.Dept. of Agriculture.; University of the Philippines.
Titles:
American Agriculturist.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Research.; Agriculture--Economic aspects.; Agriculture--International cooperation.; Agricultural laborers.; Migrant agricultural laborers--New York (State).; Wine industry--New York (State).; Agricultural education.; School lands.; Sugar beet industry--New York (State).; Student movements.; Students--Political activity.; Food supply.; Fruit industry--New York (State).; Water.; Wine and wine making.; College administrators.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Forms part of the Eastern Wine and Grape Archive. (EWGA)
Not all the material in the collection is covered by this guide.
Access Restrictions:
In part, restricted to permission of the office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
  - Letters Acknowledged by Director Charles E. Palm on His Appointment as Dean of the College of Agriculture, Effective 1 July 1959. Harriman, Averell; Adams, Morton., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Biographical Notes, Charles E. Palm. Hart, Van B., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - C.E. Palm Speech on Research., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University, Alumni Association. Adams, Morton., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Alumni Association. Adams, Morton; Myers, William I.; New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Peterson, Arthur H., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Packaging Research, Agricultural Economics. Brunk, Max E.; Packaging Foundation, Inc.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fruit Farm Management Letter. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Agricultural Engineering. Gibson, Anson W.; French, Orval C.; Myers, William I.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Engineering., 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Committee for Agriculture. Bailey, Liberty Hyde., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bailey Centennial. Malott, Deane W.; Myers, William I.; Lawrence, George H.M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Bailey Hortorium; Liberty Hyde Bailey Centennial., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bradfield, Richard. Colwell, William E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agronomy., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1959-60, Conference Board, Geneva and Ithaca. New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1959-60, State University, Agriculture, Geneva and Ithaca. New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Business Office. Peterson, Arthur H.; Quinn, William M., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Agricultural Council Meeting, Spring 1959. Kent, George C.; Atwood, Sanford S.; New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations; New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - College Fund, Dean's Income 1958-59., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Procedures., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Ad Hoc Committee in Agriculture. Federer, Walter T.; Jensen, Neal F.; Butts, George S.; Bruckner, Jacob H.; Stutz, Frederick H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Ad Hoc Committee; Practice requirements., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 23-25)
  - Ad Hoc Committee, Curriculum and Graduate Requirements. Federer, Walter T.; New York State College of Agriculture, Ad Hoc Committee., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Committees, Faculties of Agriculture and Home Economics., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Scholarship Committee. Stanton, Bernard F., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Communications Project. Ward, William B., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Kennedy, W. Keith., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Countryman. Dervin, Brenda L., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Letter to Department Heads for Suggestions of Men for Consideration for the Position of Assistant or Associate Director of Research. Brady, Nyle C.; Personius, Catherine J.; Myers, William I.; Boynton, Damon; Canoyer, Helen G., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Dairy Economics., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Endowment Income, College of Agriculture., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Extension Specialists1 Workshop, 13-17 April 1949. Bond, Maurice C.; Cummings, Gordon J.; Hanks, Elton K.; New York State, Cooperative Extension Service., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Extension Training and Information Reorganization. Bond, Maurice C.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Palm, Extension Workshop., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Comparative Extension. Stutz, Frederick H.; New York State Comparative Extension Service., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - County Agricultural Agents, State Leader's Office, Extension. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Cooperative and Comparative Extension. Bond, Maurice C.; Stutz, Frederick H.; Mosher, Arthur; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; New York State Comparative Extension Service., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - North Country Experiment Station. Myers, William I.; Fake, Kenneth H.; Kennedy, W. Keith; New York State Grange., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Ithaca News Releases., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station, Lists of Projects by Department., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Vocational Agriculture Curriculum., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - New York State College of Agriculture Council, Fall Meeting., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Numbers of Staff Employees, New York State College of Agriculture., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Farm and Home Week, News Releases., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Colleges of Forestry and Agriculture, Homer Report. Swanson, Gustav A.; Shirley, Hardy L.; Wildlife conservation., 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - New York State College of Home Economics Advisory Council. Severinghaus, Leslie R., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Talks by William I. Myers. Myers, William I., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Mann Library. Powell, Whiton; Canoyer, Helen G.; Farm and Home Week., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Parents Weekend Program., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Press Service Clippings., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Public Relations Office, Foreign Visitors., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Poultry Husbandry. Bruckner, Jacob H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Poultry Husbandry., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Professional Employees., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Profile of Entering Class. Harden, Leigh H.; New York State College of Agriculture Office of Resident Instruction., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Cornell Nutrition Conference, Buffalo. Hill, Fred W.; Cornell Nutrition Conference for Feed Manufacturers., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - A.W. Gibson, Ad Hoc Committee, Resident Instruction. Gibson, Anson W.; Tyler, Howard S.; New York State College of Agriculture Office of Resident Instruction., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Cornell University Report to Corporations. Cliggott, Richard T., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Rural Education., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Space Assignments. Myers, William I., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - SUNY Board of Trustees., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Traveling Fellowships., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Cornell Veg News., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Veterinary College Council. Hagan, William A.; New York State Veterinary College Council., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Proposal for a Cornell Water Resources Center. Peterson, Arthur H., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Agribusiness Outlook., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Alfalfa Weevil. Foster, Edward S., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Agriculturist Foundation. Cosline, Hugh L.; Ingalls, Irving W.; Eastman, Edward R., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Apple Institute News., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "The Atom and the Life Sciences" Talk by W.F. Libby. Libby, Willard F.; United States Atomic Energy Commission; Atomic energy., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Banker's School of Agriculture. Peabody, Myron C.; Federal Land Banks of Springfield; American Bankers Association., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Benson's Talks. Peterson, E.L., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations, Legislative Program., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Corn, Industries Publication., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dairy Council Digests., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Early History, College of Agriculture. Myers, William I.; Cornell University Register., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Economic Handbook and Outlook., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Eggs. Bruckner, Jacob H.; Grange League Federation., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Electric Farming News Exchange., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Entomological Society of America. Smith, Edward H.; McKelvey, John J.; Rockefeller Foundation., 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Entomological Society of America. Knight, Kenneth L.; William O. Buettner Memorial Building., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Fallon, Edmund H., Marketing Talk. Bond, Maurice C., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - New York State Farm Bureau. Foster, Edward S., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Farm Labor Management. Hopper, Nelson F.; Myers, William I.; New York State Employment Service; Farm labor., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Food Industry College Training Conference., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Ford Foundation Program. Ford Foundation., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Grange League Federation Research. Stiles, J.W., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Grange League Federation Calendar for 1959-60. Taber, Paul., 191959 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Grange League Federation Poultry Program. Ranney, Warren A.; Fallon, Edmund H., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Grocery Manufacturers of America, Inc. Atchley, Frank M.; Myers, William I., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Gypsy Moth. Swanson, Gustav A.; Bruchhausen, Walter; Schwardt, Herbert H.; Carey, Daniel J.; Frassinelli, Attilio R.; Benson, Ezra Taft; Wickham, Donald J.; Kirk, Edwin W.; Burgess, Emory D.; New York State, Dept, of Agriculture and Markets; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Entomology and Limnology; S.B. Penick and Company; DDT; Sevin; Insecticides; Gypsy Moth., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - High School Science Programs. Kingsbury, John M., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Horticultural Society News. New York State Horticultural Society., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Horticultural Society, Syracuse Talk. Dalrymple, Daniel M.; Birdsall, Webster J.; Rockefeller, Nelson A.; New York State Horticultural Society; New York State Agricultural Society., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Health Insurance., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Ho-Nun-De-Kah., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Irrigation Notes. Kennedy, W. Keith., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Land Grant College Committee. American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Legislation Folder, Growth Chambers. Adams, Morton., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Liberia. Weeks, Rochefort L.; Bond, Maurice C.; Stutz, Frederick H.; Atwood, Sanford S.; Univ. of Liberia., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Livestock Advisory Committee., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Livestock Residue Program. Gyrisco, George G.; Sevin., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Long Island Duck Research. Bruckner, Jacob H.; Peterson, Arthur H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Poultry Husbandry., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Marketing Manual., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - McDonald Farms, Animal Husbandry. Myers, William I.; McDonald, James M.; Trimberger, George W.; Turk, Kenneth L.; J.M. McDonald Foundation; McDonald Farms., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Metropolitan Milk Producers News., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Milk Marketing., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - National Dairy Council., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Natural Areas. Swanson, Gustav A.; Clausen, Robert T.; Malott, Deane W.; Kellogg, Peter Paul; Frost, Joseph N., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Natural Science Program. Kingsbury, John M., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - NE 36. Starnes, Ordway; Kerr, T.W.; McGovran, E.R.; NE 36; Pesticide residues., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - New York State Savings Bond Advisory Committee., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Organization of Education in New York. Hurd, T. Norman., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Plant Nematode Program. Kent, George C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Pathology., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Plateau Country, Farm Management Survey., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Potato Marketing Agreements. Hedlund, Glenn W.; Evans, H.J.; Potato Research Conference; Potato marketing; Potato industry., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Potato News. Empire State Potato Club., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Sigma Xi. Hewitt, Oliver H., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Social, Economic and Organizational Changes in the Population. Larson, Olaf F., 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Vegetable Production in New York, Fresh and Processed:, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - President's Office. Malott, Deane W.; Hedlund, Glenn W.; Hurd, T. Norman; French, Orval C.; Curriculum; Libraries., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Provost S.S. Atwood. Atwood, Sanford S.; Pirnie, Alexander., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Vice President, Development Office. Bruska, Walter G.; Zwingle, J.L.; Gibson, Anson W.; National Science Foundation; Cornell University, Council., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs. Summerskill, John; Gibson, Anson W.; Fisher, Max; New York State College of Agriculture, Ag-Domecon., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Vice President, Research. Wright, T. P.; Cornell University, Industry Research Park., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Office of the Dean. Barton, Donald W.; New York State College of Agriculture Farm and Home Week; Suffolk County Potato Commodity Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Dean Palm., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Dean Palm, Personal. Gibson, Anson W.; Univ. of Arkansas., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Undergraduate Deans' Meetings. Malott, Deane W.; Atwood, Sanford S., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, Memorandum to Deans. Srb, Adrian M., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Admissions. Williams, Herbert H.; Cornell University, Office of Admissions., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Profile Entering Class, 1960., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Controller A.H. Peterson. Peterson, Arthur H.; Boynton, Damon; Stutz, Frederick H.; Brady, Nyle C.; Cornell University, Office of the Controller., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Climbing Vine Peaches. Meigs, Robert B.; American Nursery Sales Company., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Department Heads Meeting. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Pathology., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Finance and Business Office. Cornell University, Office of Finance and Business., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Alumni Day, Recruitment of Students. Gibson, Anson W., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Alumni Association. Adams, Morton; Hopper, Nelson F.; New York State College of Agriculture, Alumni Association., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - University Organizations, Alumni Office. Cornell University, International Projects Committee; Cornell University, Foreign Student Office., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Office of the Registrar. Cornell University, Office of the Registrar., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Economics. Hedlund, Glenn W.; Spencer, Leland; Myers, William I.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Economics., 1953-1960 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - E.K. Hanks. Hanks, Elton K.; Myers, William I.; Soviet Agricultural Delegation., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Agricultural Engineering. French, Orval C.; Fricke, Daniel H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Engineering; United States Dept, of Agriculture, Agricultural Research Service., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Agricultural Engineering News. Markwardt, Everett D., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Agricultural Advisory Committee. Sherman, William H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Agricultural Advisory Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Agronomy Council. Brady, Nyle C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Agronomy Advisory Committee., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Agronomy Council. Brady, Nyle C.; Cline, Marlin G.; Myers, William I.; Bradfield, Richard; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agronomy; New York State Soil Conservation Committee; Cornell Weed Day., 1953-1960 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Animal Husbandry. Turk, Kenneth L.; Smith, S.E.; McCay, Clive; Myers, William I.; Albrechtsen, Raymond; Trimberger, George W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Animal Husbandry., 1954-1960 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Bailey Hortorium. Lawrence, George H.M.; Powell, Whiton; MacDaniels, Laurence H.; Stone, Robert G; Malott, Deane W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Bailey Hortorium; New York State College of Agriculture, Committee for the Bailey Hortorium; Liberty Hyde Bailey Memorial Fund., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey Hortorium Library. Powell, Whiton., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Biochemistry and Nutrition. Williams, Harold H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Biochemistry and Nutrition., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Supplemental Budget 1960., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)